{"data":[{"question":"What is the higher mountain in the world?\n\u00a0","a":"What","b":"is","c":"higher","d":"in","answer":"3","explain":"- Higher-> highest","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"I wish my mother gives me presents more often.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"wish","b":"gives","c":"me","d":"more often","answer":"2","explain":"- Gives-> gave","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"The teacher was pleasing with the result of your examination.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"The","b":"was","c":"pleasing","d":"of","answer":"3","explain":"- Pleasing-> pleased","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"The little boy didn't know how lacing his shoes.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"The little boy","b":"didn't","c":"how","d":"lacing","answer":"4","explain":"- Lacing-> to lace","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"You are quite so thin that you can slip between the bars.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"are","b":"quite so","c":"can slip","d":"between","answer":"2","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"To turn on the light, I was surprised at what I saw.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"To turn","b":"on","c":"was","d":"at","answer":"1","explain":"- To turn-> Turning","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"I would rather live on a farm than to live in a city.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"would rather","b":"live","c":"on","d":"to live","answer":"4","explain":"- To live-> live","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"The school library is free and open for all the pupils and teaching staff.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"is","b":"and","c":"for","d":"all","answer":"3","explain":"- For-> to","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Why don't you borrow books in the local lending library?\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Why","b":"don't","c":"borrow","d":"in","answer":"4","explain":"- In-> from","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"He had to admit that there were something in what mother kept saying.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"admit","b":"were","c":"what","d":"saying","answer":"2","explain":"- Were-> be\/ should be","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"}]}